Guide to the American Veterans Committee records, 1942-2002 MS2144
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Financial, legal, and operational records, 1948-2001; MS2144 Series 6
  - Indritz legal papers, 1943-1999; MS2144 Series 6, Subseries 2 (Box 133, Box 131, Box 132, Box 129, Box 130, Box 127, Box 128, Box 125, Box 126)
    - Pittsburgh Press v. Pittsburgh Commission on Human Relations, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Racial discrimination in Washington, DC, hotels and restaurants [1/3], 1954 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Racial discrimination in Washington, DC, hotels and restaurants [2/3], 1954 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Racial discrimination in Washington, DC, hotels and restaurants [3/3], 1954 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Rice v. Sioux City Memorial Park Cemetary, 1954 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Runyon v. McCrary, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Taxes, 1979-1984 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Thompson Restaurant case, 1954 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Veterans law, undated (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Washington Chapter 2, 1946-1947 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - WEAL Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Willenz annuity [1/2], 1986-1990 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Willenz annuity [2/2], 1986-1990 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Women veterans' memorial, 1986 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Women veterans' project, 1978-1980 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - AVA-AVC/Deavenport estate case, 1944-1974; MS2144 Series 6, Subseries 3 (Box 138, Box 139, Box 136, Box 137, Box 134, Box 135)
    - AVA - AVC articles of a merger, 1972 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - AVA - AVC correspondence, 1949 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - AVA - AVC documents (copies) [1/2], undated (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - AVA - AVC documents (copies) [2/2], undated (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate [1/6], 1972-1974 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate [2/6], 1972-1974 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate [3/6], 1972-1974 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate [4/6], 1972-1974 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate [5/6], 1972-1974 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate [6/6], 1972-1974 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate - bank records [1/2], 1974-1975 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate - bank records [2/2], 1974-1975 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate - correspondence [1/2], 1971-1972 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate - correspondence [2/2], 1971-1972 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate - correspondence with AMVETS and Disabled American Veterans, 1972 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate - expenses, 1972-1974 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate- expenses [2/2], 1972-1974 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - AVA - AVC merger, 1972 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate- legal research [1/2], undated (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate- legal research [2/2], undated (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - AVA - AVC/Deavenport estate- record of attorney's work, undated (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Deavenport case documents (copies) [1/4], undated (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Deavenport case documents (copies) [2/4], undated (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Deavenport case documents (copies) [3/4], undated (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Deavenport case documents (copies) [4/4], undated (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Deavenport fund, 1973-1975 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Deavenport wills, 1965 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Explanation of Deavenport will, 1965 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Probate of the Last Will and Testament of M. Gertrude Deavenport [1/2], 1971 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Probate of the Last Will and Testament of M. Gertrude Deavenport [2/2], 1971 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - AVC v. AVC case, 1990-1994; MS2144 Series 6, Subseries 4 (Box 141, Box 142, Box 253, Box 140, Box 254)
    - AVC v. AVC [1/18], 1990-1994 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - AVC v. AVC [2/18], 1990-1994 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - AVC v. AVC [3/18], 1990-1994 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - AVC v. AVC [4/18], 1990-1994 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - AVC v. AVC [5/18], 1990-1994 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - AVC v. AVC [6/18], 1990-1994 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - AVC v. AVC [7/18], 1990-1994 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - AVC v. AVC [8/18], 1990-1994 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - AVC v. AVC [9/18], 1990-1994 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - AVC v. AVC [10/18], 1990-1994 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - AVC v. AVC [11/18], 1990-1994 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - AVC v. AVC [12/18], 1990-1994 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - AVC v. AVC [13/18], 1990-1994 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - AVC v. AVC [14/18], 1990-1994 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - AVC v. AVC [15/18], 1990-1994 (Box 253, Folder 22)
    - AVC v. AVC [16/18], 1990-1994 (Box 253, Folder 23)
    - AVC v. AVC [17/18], 1990-1994 (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - AVC v. AVC [18/18], 1990-1994 (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - Amicus briefs, 1947-1999; MS2144 Series 6, Subseries 5 (Box 143, Box 144)
    - Amicus curiae briefs, 1951-1954 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Amicus curiae briefs [1/3], 1967-1987 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Amicus curiae briefs [2/3], 1967-1987 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Amicus curiae briefs [3/3], 1967-1987 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Amicus curiae briefs [1/2], 1984-1999 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Amicus curiae briefs [2/2], 1984-1999 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Lists of amicus curiae briefs, 1948-1992 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Public school segregation, 1954 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Taxation v. Regan, 1981 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Walters v. National Association of Radiation Survivors, 1984-1985 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Walters v. National Association of Radiation Survivors [1/2], 1985 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Walters v. National Association of Radiation Survivors [2/2], 1985 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Dousseau Trust, 1992-1994; MS2144 Series 6, Subseries 6 (Box 145, Box 146, Box 147)
    - Dousseau Trust [3/14], 1992-1994 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Dousseau Trust [4/14], 1992-1994 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Dousseau Trust [5/14], 1992-1994 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Dousseau Trust [6/14], 1992-1994 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Dousseau Trust [7/14], 1992-1994 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Dousseau Trust [8/14], 1992-1994 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Dousseau Trust [9/14], 1992-1994 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Dousseau Trust [10/14], 1992-1994 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Dousseau Trust [11/14], 1992-1994 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Dousseau Trust [12/14], 1992-1994 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Dousseau Trust [13/14], 1992-1994 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Dousseau Trust [14/14], 1992-1994 (Box 147, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1946-2002; MS2144 Series 7
  This series includes incoming and outgoing correspondence, primarily from AVC executive director June Willenz but also from AVC local and national leaders including Paul Cooke, Ben Neufeld, Gus Tyler, Frank Weil, Hubert Will, and others. It also includes AVC correspondence with the Department of the Army, Department of Defense, Department of State, and the Veterans Administration.
  Correspondence can also be found in many other series according to its subject matter. This correspondence was gathered intentionally within correspondence files by its creators and/or recipients.
  - General correspondence, 1945-1999; MS2144 Series 7, Subseries 1 (Box 152, Box 153, Box 151, Box 149, Box 150, Box 154, Box 148)
    - 24th Amendment correspondence - Rudolf Sobernheim, 1962-1963 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Akaka, Senator Daniel - John Tagami - correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Bernstein, Arthur - correspondence, 1990; Series 7 (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - Berresford, Susan - correspondence, 1982-1996 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Birnbaum, Irving, and Gross, Murray - correspondence [1/2], 1962-1963 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Birnbaum, Irving, and Gross, Murray - correspondence [2/2], 1962-1963 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Board correspondence, 1954-1993 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Congratulatory correspondence, 1948 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence on veterans' issues, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Dancer, Cliff (National Field Secretary) - correspondence, 1948 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Department of the Army - correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Department of Defense - correspondence, 1964 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Department of State - correspondence, 1945-1978 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Dialogue on National Service - correspondence, 1989 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Feldman, Arnold - correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Freeman, Arthur - correspondence, 1973-1995 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - General AVC correspondence [1/2], 1945-1961 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - General AVC correspondence [2/2], 1945-1961 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - General AVC correspondence, 1962-1975 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - General AVC correspondence [1/2], 1976-1977 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - General AVC correspondence [2/2], 1976-1977 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - General AVC correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - General AVC correspondence [1/3], 1982-1998 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - General AVC correspondence [2/3], 1982-1998 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - General AVC correspondence [3/3], 1982-1998 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - General AVC correspondence, 1958-1995; Series 7 (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - Gray, Carl Jr. (VA) - correspondence, 1948-1954 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Harrison, Gibert - correspondence, 1949 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Heisler, Tibor - correspondence, 1965-1998; Series 7 (Box 259, Folder 10)
    - Kennedy, Edward - correspondence, 1973 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Indritz, Phineas - correspondence, 1954-1977 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Korn, Fannie Mayer - correspondence, 1949-1956 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Levine, Mickey - correspondence, 1962 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Masi, Fidelia (Dale) - correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Nathan, Robert - correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - National Advisory Council - correspondence, 1965-1974 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Neufeld, Ben - correspondence, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Neufeld, Ben - correspondence [1/2], 1979-1999 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Neufeld, Ben - correspondence [2/2], 1979-1999 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Neufield, Ben - correspondence, 1990; Series 7 (Box 259, Folder 11)
    - O'Brien, Thomas - correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Press correspondence, 1968-1982 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Rice, Andrew - correspondence, 1954 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Rosen, Saul - correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Silvers, Hal - correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Spingarn, Jerome (National Counsel) - correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Stars and Stripes - correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Stillman, John - correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Tyler, Gus - correspondence, 1967-1980 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Tyler, Gus - correspondence [1/2], 1981-2001 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Tyler, Gus - correspondence [2/2], 1981-2001 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Tyler, Gus - correspondence, 1992; Series 7 (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - VA correspondence, 1946-1953 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - VA correspondence (Max Cleland), 1977 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - VA correspondence (Rufus Wilson), 1978 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Washington, D.C., affairs - correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - The Washington Post - correspondence, 1952-1976 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Weil, Frank - correspondence, 1963-1977 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Weil, Frank - correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - White House correspondence, 1946-1951 (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - White House correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - White House correspondence, 1993 (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Women in Congress - correspondence, 1980 (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Will, Hubert - correspondence [1/2], 1954-1969 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Will, Hubert - correspondence [2/2], 1954-1969 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Will, Hubert - correspondence, 1979-1988 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Will, Hubert - correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Cooke, Paul -- correspondence, 1950-2002; MS2144 Series 7, Subseries 2 (Box 155, Box 156)
    - Cooke, Paul - correspondence [1/2], 1960-1962 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Cooke, Paul - correspondence [2/2], 1960-1962 (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Cooke, Paul - correspondence [1/2], 1963-1965 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Cooke, Paul - correspondence [2/2], 1963-1965 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Cooke, Paul - correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Cooke, Paul - correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Cooke, Paul - correspondence, 1980-1989 (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Cooke, Paul - correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Cooke, Paul - correspondence, 2001-2002 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Willenz, June -- correspondence, 1966-1999; MS2144 Series 7, Subseries 3 (Box 158, Box 157, Box 165, Box 164, Box 161, Box 160, Box 159, Box 163, Box 162, Box 166)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/2], 1978-1979 (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/2], 1978-1979 (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/2], 01/1980-07/1980 (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/2], 01/1980-07/1980 (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/2], 08/1980-12/1980 (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/2], 08/1980-12/1980 (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 01/1981 (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/2], 02/1981-03/1981 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/2], 02/1981-03/1981 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/2], 04/1981-07/1981 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/2], 04/1981-07/1981 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/2], 08/1981-12/1981 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/2], 08/1981-12/1981 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 01/1982-03/1982 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 04/1982-06/1982 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 07/1982-09/1982 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 10/1982-01/1983 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 02/1983-08/1983 (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 09/1983-10/1983 (Box 161, Folder 3)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/2], 11/1983-03/1984 (Box 161, Folder 4)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/2], 11/1983-03/1984 (Box 161, Folder 5)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/2], 04/1984-09/1984 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/2], 04/1984-09/1984 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/3], 10/1984-03/1985 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/3], 10/1984-03/1985 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [3/3], 10/1984-03/1985 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 04/1985-08/1985 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 09/1985-12/1985 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 01/1986-05/1986 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/2], 06/1986-12/1986 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/2], 06/1986-12/1986 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 1987 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [1/2], 1988-1989 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence [2/2], 1988-1989 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, 1985-1998; Series 7 (Box 259, Folder 13)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, A - F, 1974-1991 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, G - R, 1975-1982 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence, S - Y, 1975-1978 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - June Willenz file [1/2], 1983-2000; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - June Willenz file [2/2], 2000-2002; Seroes 7 Subseries 3 (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with board members, 1976-1979 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Willenz, June - correspondence with Max Cleland, 1977-1980 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - Willenz, June - postcards, 1982-1983 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence from June Willenz [1/10], 2001-2002; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence from June Willenz [2/10], 1998; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from June Willenz [3/10], 1998; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence from June Willenz [4/10], 1997-1998; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence from June Willenz [5/10], 1996-1997; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence from June Willenz [6/10], 1995-1996; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence from June Willenz [7/10], 1995; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from June Willenz [8/10], 1994-1995; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence from June Willenz [9/10], 1994; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence from June Willenz [10/10], 1992-1994; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 264, Folder 4)
- Events, 1946-2000; MS2144 Series 8
  This series includes printed programs, invitations, correspondence, and planning materials relating to major AVC events. This encompasses events such as the National Convention, Bill of Rights Dinners, Breakfast and Luncheon meeting series, special conferences, and receptions. This series does not include minutes from these events; where available, they are in series 4.
  - Constitutional Convention (Des Moines, Iowa), 06/1947 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - 2nd National Convention (Milwaukee, WI), 06/1947 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - 3rd National Convention (Cleveland, OH), 11/1948 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - 4th National Convention (Chicago, IL), 11/1949 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - 5th National Convention (New York, NY), 05/31/1951-06/03/1951 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - 10th Anniversary Convention (Atlantic City, NJ), 12/1953 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - 8th National Convention (Boston, MA), 12/1954 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - 12th National Convention (Monticello, NY), 05/1959 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - 13th National Convention (Atlantic City, NJ), 06/1960 (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - 14th National Convention (New York, NY), 05/1961 (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - 15th National Convention (Atlantic City, NJ), 06/1962 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - 20th Anniversary Convention (Washington, DC), 06/1963 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - National Convention, 1966 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - National Convention (Atlantic City, NJ), 06/1967 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - 25th Anniversary Convention (South Fallsburg, NY), 06/1968 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - 26th Anniversary Convention (Atlantic City, NJ), 06/1969 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - 23rd National Convention (Washington, DC), 06/1970 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - 25th Des Moines Anniversary Convention (Des Moines, Iowa), 06/1971 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - 28th Anniversary Convention (New York, NY), 06/1972 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - 29th Anniversary Convention (Atlantic City, NJ), 06/1973 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - 30th Anniversary Convention (South Fallsburg, NY), 06/1974 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - 31st Anniversary Convention (South Fallsburg, NY), 06/1975 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Bicentennial Celebration Convention (Washington, DC), 06/1976 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - 33rd Anniversary Convention (Tamiment, PA), 06/1977 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - 34th Anniversary Convention (The Poconos, PA), 06/1978 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - 35th Anniversary Convention (Forest Park, PA) [1/4], 06/1979 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - 35th Anniversary Convention (Forest Park, PA) [2/4], 06/1979 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - 35th Anniversary Convention (Forest Park, PA) [3/4], 06/1979 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - 35th Anniversary Convention (Forest Park, PA) [4/4], 06/1979 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - 36th Anniversary Convention (Forest Park, PA) [1/4], 06/1980 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - 36th Anniversary Convention (Forest Park, PA) [2/4], 06/1980 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - 36th Anniversary Convention (Forest Park, PA) [3/4], 06/1980 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - 36th Anniversary Convention (Forest Park, PA) [4/4], 06/1980 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - 37th Anniversary Convention (The Poconos, PA), 06/1981 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - 38th Anniversary Convention (The Poconos, PA), 06/1982 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - 39th Anniversary Convention (Liberty, NY) [1/2], 06/1983 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - 39th Anniversary Convention (Liberty, NY) [2/2], 06/1983 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - 40th Anniversary Convention (The Poconos, PA), 06/1984-07/1984 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - National Convention (Unity House, PA), 06/1985 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Reunion Convention (Washington, DC), 09/1989 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - 50th Anniversary Convention, 06/18/1994 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - 6th Annual Bill of Rights Dinner, 06/07/1952 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - 7th Annual Bill of Rights Dinner, 09/24/1953 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - 8th Annual Bill of Rights Dinner, 09/17/1954 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - 9th Annual Bill of Rights Dinner, 10/07/1955 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - 10th Bill of Rights Award Dinner, 03/14/1958 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - 11th Bill of Rights Award Dinner, 02/21/1959 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - 12th Annual Bill of Rights Dinner, 03/03/1961 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - 13th Annual Bill of Rights Dinner, 03/03/1962 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Bill of Rights Dinner, 03/07/1964 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Breakfast and Luncheon Meeting Series, 1957-1966 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Breakfast and Luncheon Meeting Series, 09/25/1990-12/16/1993 (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Breakfast and Luncheon Meeting Series, 01/1994-10/1995 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Breakfast and Luncheon Meeting Series, 04/03/1996-10/1997 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Breakfast and Luncheon Meeting Series, 1998-2000 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - National Planning Committee Dinner, 11/14/1947 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - National Veterans Housing Conference, 02/29/1948-03/01/1948 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Middlebury College Conference, 1948 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - 3rd Anniversary Banquet, 06/05/1948 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - A Showing of Paintings by Washington Artists, 02/1952 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Encampment for Citizenship, 1953 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Annual Dinner, 02/11/1953 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - "The Human Equation" Art Exhibit, 1953 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Annual Open Meeting, 04/03/1954 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - Roy Cohn Dinner, 07/1954 (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - 6th Annual Art Exhibit - "Children's Art Exhibit", 10/1954 (Box 174, Folder 13)
  - Freedom Agenda Regional Conferences, 02/1955-04/1955 (Box 174, Folder 14)
  - Hungarian Reception, 01/19/1957 (Box 174, Folder 15)
  - 14th Annual Encampment for Citizenship, 1959 (Box 174, Folder 16)
  - Nat'l Affairs Committee Working Conference on Reapportionment, 11/28/1960 (Box 174, Folder 17)
  - National Conference on the Draft, 11/1966 (Box 174, Folder 18)
  - Human Rights of Man in Uniform, 1967 (Box 174, Folder 19)
  - Human Rights of Man in Uniform, 06/1968 (Box 174, Folder 20)
  - White House Conference on Food, Nutrition, and Health, 1969 (Box 174, Folder 21)
  - Human Rights of Man in Uniform, 11/1969 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Human Rights of Man in Uniform [1/2], 1970 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Human Rights of Man in Uniform [2/2], 1970 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - White House Conference on Youth, 1971 (Box 175, Folder 4)